http://www.wellhunghammocks.com/pages/terms-conditions

Chair Hammock Frame
Need Help?
Chair Hammock Frame
Need Help?
Chair Hammock Frame
Need Help?
Terms & Conditions
Welcome to the wellhunghammocks.com website terms and conditions for use. Please read through the nitty gritty below...
These terms and conditions apply to the use of this Website  and by accessing this Website and/or placing an order you agree to be bound by  the terms and conditions set out below.
If you do not agree to be bound by  these terms and conditions you may not use or access this Website.
Definitions
“Conditions" means these terms and conditions; "Website" means  the website located at www.wellhunghammocks.com or www.wellhunghammocks.co.uk or any subsequent URL which may replace it;  "Product" means a product displayed for sale on the Website;  "Users" means the users of the Website collectively; "Personal  Information" means the details provided by you on registration;  "We/Us/Our" means Well Hung Hammocks; "Cookies" means small  text files which our Website places on your computer's hard drive to store information  about your shopping session and to identify your computer; "United  Kingdom" means England, Wales, Scotland, Northern Ireland and the Channel  Islands and "You" means a user of this Website.
Registration
You warrant that: The Personal Information which You are required to  provide when You register as a customer is true, accurate, current and complete  in all respects; and You will notify Us immediately of any changes to the  Personal Information by contacting Us by e-mail, or calling Us on +44 7930 494853  between 9am-9pm. You agree not to impersonate any other person or entity or to  use a false name or a name that You are not authorised to use.
IndemnityYou agree fully to indemnify, defend and hold Us, and Our officers,  directors, employees, agents and suppliers, harmless immediately on demand,  from and against all claims, liability, damages, losses, costs and expenses,  including reasonable legal fees, arising out of any breach of the Conditions by  You or any other liabilities arising out of your use of this Website, or the  use by any other person accessing the Website using your shopping account  and/or your Personal Information.
Our rightsWe reserve the right to modify or withdraw, temporarily or permanently,  this Website (or any part thereof) with or without notice to You and You confirm  that We shall not be liable to You or any third party for any modification to  or withdrawal of the Website; and/or change of the Conditions from time to  time, and your continued use of the Website (or any part thereof) following  such change shall be deemed to be your acceptance of such change. It is your  responsibility to check regularly to determine whether the Conditions have been  changed. If You do not agree to any change to the Conditions then You must  immediately stop using the Website.
Availability of the WebsiteAlthough We aim to offer you the best service possible, We make no  promise that the services at this Website will meet your requirements. Well  Hung Hammocks cannot guarantee that the service will be fault free. If a fault  occurs in the service you should report it to info@wellhunghammocks.com and We will attempt to correct the fault as soon as We reasonably can. Your  access to the Website may be occasionally restricted to allow for repairs,  maintenance or the introduction of new facilities or services. We will attempt  to restore the service as soon as We reasonably can.
Third party linksTo provide increased value to our Users, We may provide links to other  websites or resources for You to access at your sole discretion. You  acknowledge and agree that, as You have chosen to enter the linked website We  are not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources,  and do not review or endorse and are not responsible or liable, directly or  indirectly, for (i) the privacy practices of such websites, (ii) the content of  such websites, including (without limitation) any advertising, content,  products, goods or other materials or services on or available from such  websites or resources or (iii) the use to which others make of these websites  or resources, nor for any damage, loss or offence caused or alleged to be  caused by, or in connection with, the use of or reliance on any such  advertising, content, products, goods or other materials or services available  on such external websites or resources.
PrivacyWe will treat all your Personal Information as confidential (although we  reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out  below). We will keep it in a secure environment on Our server and We will fully  comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation in place  (7/12/06).  When You shop on this Website, We will ask You to input and will collect  Personal Information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing  address, delivery address, telephone number, product selections and a password.  Credit card and other payment information will be collected using secure third  party payment-gateway providers. We may also collect information about where  You are on the internet (e.g. the URL You came from, IP address, domain types  like .co.uk and .com), your browser type, the country where your computer is  located, the pages of Our Website that were viewed during your visit and any  search terms that You entered on the Website. We may collect this information  even if You do not register with Us. You should be aware that this site is  being monitored and may capture information about your visit that will help Us  improve the quality of Our service. We use your information only for the following purposes:
Processing your orders For statistical or survey purposes to improve this  Website and Our services to You, To serve website content to You,To administer this website and If You consent, to notify You of products or special  offers that may be of interest to You.You agree that You do not object to us contacting you for any of the  above purposes whether by telephone, e-mail or in writing and You confirm that  You do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of  your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive)  Regulations 2003. In the event that You do not wish to be contacted for such  purposes, ensure that You email info@wellhunghammocks.com. You may  unsubscribe from Our contact list at any time by replying to a promotional  e-mail with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line, by e-mailing  Us at info@wellhunghammocks.com or telephoning Us on +44 7930 494853 between  9am-9pm,. Your Personal Information may be disclosed to other businesses and to  reputable third parties who will help process your order. Well Hung Hammocks  requires all such third parties to treat your personal information as fully  confidential and to fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and  consumer legislation from time to time in place. We will not release your  Personal Information to any company for mailing or marketing purposes. You should be aware that if We are requested by the police or any other  regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities  to provide your Personal Information and /or User Information, We are entitled to do so.We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session to  personalise your experience and so that You may retrieve your shopping basket  at any time - if you do not accept Cookies You will be unable to use this  Website.Any material, information or other communication You transmit or post to  this site (unless it is Personal Information or is related to your order)  will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary and may be reproduced  by Well Hung Hammocks  to further its cause, unless You tell Us otherwise  in writing. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to Our  privacy policy.
OrdersWe will take all reasonable care, in so far as it is in Our power to do  so, to keep the details of your order and payment secure, but in the absence of  negligence on Our part We cannot be held liable for any loss You may suffer if  a third party procures unauthorised access to any data You provide when  accessing or ordering from the Website.To check your order status, just click on the Your account link  at the top of the page, sign in and then click on My orders.  If You find that your order has only been partially delivered, this may  be because other items are being despatched from a different location. However,  if your order is obviously incomplete, over-delivered or damaged, or if You  wish to change or cancel your order, please email info@wellhunghammocks.com or  telephone on 07930 494853 between 9am and 9pm.Customers from outside the UK will be responsible for any applicable import  taxes into their country.
Refund & Returns policy:  Unwanted itemsWe hope You will be pleased with your purchase. If for any reason You  should wish to return anything bought from Us, We will be happy to refund or  exchange a product provided it is in fully resaleable condition. Returns should  be made within 14 days and in original, undamaged packaging. Returns should be  sent to Us using the same delivery service by which they were received (or in  the case of international transactions by an equivalent service of similar cost  to that by which they were received).If We find that the Product has not been returned to Us in fully  resaleable condition, We reserve the right to refuse a refund on the item, or  deduct up to 25% of the original selling price from the refund amount. You must  bear the cost of returning the item to Us and We will not refund your original  delivery charge when a product is simply unwanted.
Please note that due to the weight of the item, We cannot accept returns and therefore offer refunds on unwanted Hammock Stands (unless faulty) so You must ensure that it is suitable for your hammock. Please check the size of your hammock if it has not been purchased from Us - any hammock purchased from Us will fit on our Stands.
Refund & Returns policy:  Faulty ItemsWe hope you will always be pleased  with your purchase however if any Products bought from Us are damaged, faulty,  or not as described We will be happy to refund or exchange such Products. In  cases of faulty, damaged or incorrect goods  being returned to Us, as well as the original cost of the item, We will refund  your original delivery charge plus the reasonable costs incurred by You in  returning said goods. Returns should be sent to Us using the same delivery  service by which they were received (or in the case of international  transactions by an equivalent service of similar cost to that by which they  were received).
If any parts of a Hammock Stand are faulty within a year of purchase please contact Us describing which piece is broken and We will replace the part free of charge.
If You do have cause for complaint We urge You to contact Us immediately  by phone (+44 7930 494853, 9am-9pm) or email (info@wellhunghammocks.com)  so that We may be able to resolve any problems You may have.
We advise customers to read any care and maintenance instructions  included with the Product (and elsewhere in this Website) to avoid any damage  due to inappropriate use. In these circumstances We are not able to offer  either a replacement or a refund. None of the above conditions affect your statutory consumer rights.
Refunds & Returns Policy: Lost/Damaged or Delayed in Transit
Any items sent by 1st class Royal Mail within the UK are expected to arrive within 2-5 working days (excluding Saturdays and Sundays) of shipment. We will not entertain any claims for refunds for mis-delivery of goods until 5 clear working days have passed from (and excluding) the day of posting - we can provide proof of posting on request. For heavier items sent by standard parcel service deliveries are expected within 3-7 working days of posting and we will not entertain any claims for mis-delivery of goods until 10 clear working days have passed from (and excluding) the day of posting. If your order has failed to arrive within the usual timescale of deliveries, please contact us and we will endeavour to help you in any way we can.
If your order is urgent, we can provide an expedited service on a case by case basis so please contact us for further information and rates.
Orders sent internationally by Royal mail International are expected to arrive within 5-10 working days. We will not entertain any claims for refunds on mis-delivered goods until 21 clear working days have passed from (and excluding) the date of posting.
You can check the status of your order at any time under your account settings. If you have any queries regarding your order or if you require an expected delivery timescale, please email info@wellhunghammocks.com or telephone +44 7930494853 between 9am-9pm.
Product Ratings / ReviewsYou must not: abuse, harass or threaten others; We do not  allow bigoted, hateful or racially offensive statements, nor do We permit  crude language; We do not allow the advocacy of any illegal activity;  You must not post or distribute any material that infringes and/or violates any  right of a third party or any law; You cannot use the product review  form for commercial purposes of any kind.We reserve the right to remove / edit  content at any  time and for any reason. By submitting any materials to Us, You automatically grant (or warrant  that the owner of such materials expressly granted) Us a perpetual,  royalty-free, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce,  modify, adapt, publish, translate, publicly perform and display, create derivative  works from and distribute such materials or incorporate such materials into any  form, medium, or technology now known or later developed throughout the  universe. In addition, You warrant that all so-called "moral rights"  in those materials have been waived.We are not responsible for, and do not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of, any opinion, advice, statement, recommendation or other  information included in any message posted on this site, unless it  has been posted by one of our representatives. Any reliance by you on any such  opinion, advice, statement, recommendation or other information shall be at  your sole risk.
Intellectual property and  right to useThe content of this Website is  protected by copyright, trade marks, database and other intellectual property  rights. You may retrieve and display the content of this Website on a computer  screen, store such content in electronic form on disk (but not any server or  other storage device connected to a network) or print one copy of such content  for your own personal, non-commercial use, provided You keep intact all and any  copyright and proprietary notices. You may not (or may not assist or facilitate  any third party to) otherwise reproduce, modify, copy or distribute or use for  commercial purposes any of the materials or content on the Website without  written permission from Us. Well Hung Hammocks is trade mark protected and no  licence is granted to you in these Terms and Conditions to use any trade mark  of  Well Hung Hammocks.  All titles and rights to Well Hung Hammocks,  wellhunghammocks.com, wellhunghammocks.co.uk and wellhunghammocks.info are  wholly owned by E.R. Burn.
Compliance with lawsThe Website may be used only for lawful purposes and in a lawful manner.  You agree to comply with all applicable laws, statutes and regulations  regarding the Website and any transactions conducted on or through the Website.
Limitation of liabilityThe Website is provided by Well  Hung Hammocks without any warranties or guarantees. You must bear the risks  associated with the use of the Internet.This Website may provide content  from other Internet sites or resources and while We try to ensure that material  included on the Website is correct, reputable and of high quality, We cannot  accept responsibility if this is not the case. We cannot guarantee the accuracy  of the information provided on this Website. We will not be responsible for any  errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of such  information or for any technical problems You may experience with this Website.  If We are informed of any inaccuracies in the material on the Website We will  attempt to correct the inaccuracies as soon as We reasonably can. We make no  warranty that the Website will meet your requirements or will be uninterrupted,  timely or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the site or the  server that makes it available are free of viruses or bugs or represents the  full functionality, accuracy, reliability of the Website. We will not be  responsible or liable to You for any loss of content or material uploaded or  transmitted through the Website. In  particular, We disclaim all liabilities in connection with the following:
Incompatibility of the Website with any of your  equipment, software or telecommunications links   technical problems including errors or interruptions  of the Website. unsuitability, unreliability or inaccuracy of the  inadequacy of the Website to meet your requirements.To the full extent allowed by  applicable law, You agree that We will not be liable to You/or any third party  for any consequential or incidental damages (including but not limited to loss  of revenue, loss of profits, loss of anticipated savings, wasted expenditure,  loss of privacy and loss of data) or any other indirect, special or punitive  damages whatsoever that arise out of or are related to this Website.Nothing in this paragraph applies  to our liability in respect of Products sold through this Website.Nothing in these Terms and  Conditions shall exclude Our liability for personal injury or death caused by  Our negligence. Our acceptance of an order takes  place on despatch of the order, at which point the purchase contract will be  made and You will be charged for your order.
LawThe Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the  laws of England and You irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the  courts of England.
ContactThe registered address of Well Hung Hammocks is 20 Breakspear Road, Ruislip, Middlesex, HA4 7QZ,  UK.
